distancelearning.edu.in 2017-04-18

# DLP India - India's Top online Distance Learning and Education Courses Provider

Our Approach to **Privacy**

DLP India (DLP India Edutech Private Limited) is committed to responsible privacy practices and to complying with Indian law. Our respect for your privacy is paramount. We have policies and procedures to ensure that all personal information is handled in accordance with Indian law. This Privacy Policy sets out our policies on the management of personal information - that is, how we collect personal information, the purposes for which we use this information, and to whom this information is disclosed.Please read this privacy policy carefully by accessing or using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to all the terms of this privacy policy and our website terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms, exit this page and do not access or use the website.Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "User" or the "End User") and how we use that information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us.

Changes to **Privacy Policy-**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the "Privacy Policy" section of the Website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. It is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

What is **personal information?**

Personal information is information that could identify you. Examples of personal information include your name, address, mobile number, education and email address.

**How do we collect and use your personal information?**

One of the main ways in which DLP India collects personal information is when you fill the enquiry/ application form & when you enrol for an admission. By filling the enquiry form you agree that DLP India (DLP India Edutech Private Limited) may use your name, email address, phone number or other data to communicate with you through calls, SMS and emails, either by itself or through any of its designates ( marketing team, franchisees, outsourcing call centres, information team, sales executive etc). 

We may utilize that information to,

* Contact the enquirer in reference to his enquiry for counseling purpose 

* Keep the complete academic record of student.

* To mail you all necessary material & complete student kit & confirmation which is when provided by the partner University.

* To keep you inform regarding any news (Exam dates, assignments, results), schemes, and informative mails.

* Contact you to obtain your feedback, surveys. 

**Sharing of Personally Identifiable Information**

We may disclose or share Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates like MITSDE, ADTU, Annamalai University, MGU, KSOU, Dr D Y Patil University and other listed on the website. We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes.

Security of **Information:**

We take security seriously and take numerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information of those who are registered of have online accounts. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your Personally Identifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selected personnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information

Privacy Policies of **Third Party Websites:**

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the respective website's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

Miscellaneous **Privacy Issues:**

Children, Minors under the age of 18 may not use the Website. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 18, and no part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.

Unsubscription 

To unsubscribe and opt out from DLP India's database, please email contact@distancelearning.edu.in with "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the subject line. You could also remove your personal information from our database by calling us at 09958934646

Disclaimer: 

* By filling the enquiry form you agree that DLP India (DLP India Edutech Private Limited) may use your name, email address, phone number or other data to communicate with you through calls, SMS and emails, either by itself or through any of its designates (franchisees, outsourcing call centres, information team, sales executive etc) 

* DLP India from here after can contact you anytime in future. 

* You may receive newsletters, e - brochures, emailers, SMS from DLP India anytime. 

* You can request to have your information modified or deleted from our records to us by sending mail to contact@distancelearning.edu.in any time if you wish to. DLP India assures you that it will not sell this information to any third party. 

* DLP India hold the complete authority to change any term and condition without any prior notice.
